Okay, so we're already on the website, since there are some products I made.
It's asking you to join newsletter, and then right now we created, there's a 15% off storewide,
and basically all I want to do right now is go through to a post or two, and purchase it.
So basically, instead of GIFs, you can just tell it to loop, like this one is, or give it a play button,
and then all of that type of content will show up down there, this is your gallery, your hero image.
That's that, I'm going to buy this one, and actually let's buy two.
These are, they're miniatures that I made, this is funny right now, I just used Google's nano-banana
to throw something together so that it didn't look completely empty.
Add to cart.
Cool, added.
Two products, they're showing up in here with the discount, we'll check out.